So this is in France. So there are a lot
of riots in France. This is just France.
This is actually pretty bad. The
blockades of French schools.
This is France.
This is in France.
Imagine
just banging on the door. Like really
just you're just banging on the door. So
here we go. France erupts and much of
the world is looking elsewhere outside
the country. You can easily miss it at
the scale. 170 demonstrators took place
in France. And this is uh yeah here's
some more of it. Uh clashes, political
arguments. Look at this here.
Oh my god.
The French always protest like this.
They've been doing it like the 70s.
These people aren't French. They're a
bunch of foreign immigrant invaders that
should be remigrated.
The overwhelming majority of these
people that are protesting at the
school, they're not French.
>> Jesus Christ.
Is it happening like that? Yeah, I don't
think so. Hard to tell who's who in
these videos. Yeah, I mean obviously
this is just like it's just chaos,
right? It's total [__] chaos. And
here's another one. Uh let's take a look
at this here. Uh young second, third
generation miners continue attacking
schools across France today. This video
is from Emilazola High School near Liel.
In the aftermath, shows students setting
a car on fire and using it to ram the
gates of a school.
Man.
Uhoh.
Uhoh. Yep. There we go. And they want
them uneducated. No, that's not that's
not the issue. Let's take a look at this
here. Meanwhile, in France, the Leonard
Defin Da Vinci School of Rubo, I I don't
know how to say his name, uh has been
set on fire as hordes of Muslim
teenagers stand around filming it.
>> Wow.
Where's Napoleon, bro?
Where is he?
Like, they got to get that guy to come
back.
They do. They got to bring that guy
Like, I mean, this is Yeah. I mean,
there's something got to happen. So, a
school teacher is attacked and chased
down the street by North African
students as riots spread across the
country. Here we go again.
[music]
Oh my god.
>> Wow. And uh you could say uh Le Panda is
Napoleon. Her party is exiled and now
she's back. Yep. True. That's very true.
And this is what's insane. Meanwhile, in
St. Dennis, France, the story is totally
insane. The city in France is primarily
populated by migrants and second
generational immigrants. Student riots
and violence have broken out across the
city. However, this is also their mayor
uh Bali Bagio, son of a a Mlealan uh
African migrant celebrating with the
riers and encouraging the destruction of
his own city. You are witnessing the
takeover and collapse of Western
civilization in real time.
>> This is the mayor.
The French media is trying to spin this
as bro is putting out fires.
As I've said, um, you know,
uh, it's crazy. Oh, this is Oh, here we
go. France. A school teacher is attacked
while trying to put out a trash can
fire. Let's take a look at this.
suspect.
Wow.
>> And you can see this is the guy, this
Einstein looking guy is like trying to
he has a fire extinguisher. He clearly
has a fire extinguisher and they're
throwing him to the ground to stop him
from putting out the fire.
Isn't that crazy?
Oh my god.
[screaming]
[cheering]
>> Welcome to France.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god.
Oh my god.
That is just unbelievable.
Streets across France are turning into
war zones as high school students from
migrant backgrounds set everything on
fire in their path.
>> [screaming]
>> This is France.
>> Man.
Man,
France has fallen. No, it hasn't.
No, I I I think that you guys
Here's the reality.
This is It's good this is happening.
It is. It's good this is happening
because if enough people see this kind
of stuff,
somebody is going to decide, you know
what? It's time to make it stop.
And that's going to be the end of it.
This is going to wake enough people up.
And again, keep in mind that you don't
need a majority.
You all you need is the military.
That's all you need. You don't need a
majority. You don't need to get these
people on your side. You don't need to
win over the approval of a bunch of
shrieking hags. All you need is the
military ability to shut this [__] down.
The militaries let them in. The
militaries were ordered to let them in.
And eventually a military might stop
listening. This isn't Beirut or Thran.
Now, this is from 2022. I'm glad I
didn't go and show that. Some of these
are inaccurately. Why are they
protesting? Let's take a look at this.
No one is brave enough to do that.
Oh, I don't know. I mean, eventually
sometimes it's just going to happen,
right? See, so this is this is one thing
that you guys might not understand is
that
nothing happens [music] until everything
happens.
One day, whenever something changes, I'm
not going to say what I think I know
what's going to happen. I do. I think I
know what's going to happen.
And when that happens,
there's going to be no stopping it. It's
just going to be over.
And do you remember the Polish guy that
said, "Give me 3 days."
Okay,
we'll see. It's going to be a goriest
day. It will happen so fast that no
other country could even react.
I agree with you. But uh the best
example was 911 when it happened.
Everyone got together and eventually
George Bush was elected. George Bush was
elected before 911. He was elected in
2000. 9/11 happened at the end of 2001.
But uh I know what you're I know what
you're saying obviously.
>> Why aren't French students blockading
schools across the country? Over 400
>> going to vague max or Kon sharing your
theory. I'm I'm going to continue vague
maxing. We're going to continue vague.
Maxer,
>> why are French students blocking schools
across the country? 400 people have been
detained, most of them miners, as
students protest overcrowded classrooms,
staff short.
>> I wonder why the classrooms are
overcrowded. Nobody could ever guess
why. Why would this ever happen,
and long school days?
Some protesters have told
>> the school is in a terrible state, so
we're going to burn down the school.
>> Right.
>> And thrown objects at least. Officers
responded with batons and tear gas. The
education minister says 76 student and
school staff have been injured has begun
with the interior. These are, as I've
said before, these are the people who
are at odds with civilization.
These are the people who I think the
these are the people who we need to as
chuds without borders stand against. It
doesn't matter if you're from Saudi
Arabia, you're from China, you're from
Ukraine, you're from Colombia. We need
to all look at these freaks and decide,
you know what? Enough is enough.
Enough's enough. We're tired of it.
We're tired of it, bro.
It literally says Antifa. Yes, that's
correct. These people are all the same
everywhere. And until we're ready to
deal with them, we're going to keep
having these problems. And also, I I
want to make one thing very clear is
that they will gain enough power to
where they can enact their pol their
policies. This is it's like think about
these people like a cancer, right? is
that the cancer will continue to grow
and if you let it grow big enough then
the cancer will kill the host. So you
have to remove the cancer before the
cancer kills the host because that's the
world that we're going towards right now
is that there is a possibility that one
of these countries will fall. Now I
don't think this is going to be a big
deal. Now why is that? Well, Hitler took
over France and now France got, you
know, France, they they they got they
got it back, right? And how did they get
it back? Well, uh, England and America
and all the other European countries
helped them get it back. So, even if one
of the countries falls, it's going to be
temporary, right? Because clearly the
other European countries will
eventually, you know, just get rid of
the invaders and then that will be the
end of it. But, uh, yeah, which others?
That's not even remotely the same. Uh, I
mean, it's it kind of is. I mean, it
kind of is. Why is Antifa called a
terrorist organization but not treated
as one? Because we have people in our
government that are full of uh that are
just full of [__] and they're massive
[__] That's why. They're just
massive [__] that are full of [__]
You really think the UK doesn't hate
France?
No, I don't think the UK hates France.
No, I don't.
I think the UK sees France as one of
their allies because they're all
Europeans.
I think that if there was no other like
there's an old saying, me against my
brother, me and my brother against my
cousin, and me and my brother and my
cousin against the world.
I mean, like really like these are these
are at least these are brothers if not
at least cousins, right? Like Yeah. Uh
we we support the Antifa. Exactly. There
is a larger there is a larger problem
that exists beyond just simply these
like, you know, oh well, what about what
Napoleon did? like that. That that's all
history. This is reality. It's
immediate.
>> As a Frenchman, the Englishmen are our
greatest foes. Therefore, our oldest
friends.
I have a lot of friends like that
myself.
>> Injured since the protest began with the
interior minister saying 48 police
officers were hurt. The government says
students have the right to protest but
have condemned the violence. Why are
French students
>> unbelievable to see this happen? It is.
The entire left apparatus in America has
been vilifying and gaslighting and it's
antagonizing their own neighbor for the
last decade and a half. Yeah. And I just
want to let you guys know that there is
a way out of this. There's a way out of
this and it would happen in one year.
>> French teenagers set fire to rubbish
bins and hurled projectiles and clashes
with French Tuesday as they kept up a
blockade of high schools to demand
better conditions. Uh-huh.
>> Since last week, high school students
across France staged protests outside
their schools over grievances, including
timets, class sizes, and a shortage of
teachers, as well as overheated
classrooms in the wake of the recent
heat waves.
>> Yeah,
we saw this one before.
>> What is this? What is this expedition 33
[__] they've got on the screen here?
What does this say?
What does this say? I I don't know what
the [__] this says.
It says you're gay.
It says we're gay and [__]
It says we're all French and we're gay.
Okay, that's what I thought.
Why do they keep saying teenagers?
>> The reason why is because the media
doesn't want to admit that a lot of this
unrest is caused primarily by migrants
and descendants of migrants that have
not assimilated and are not culturally,
ethnically or in any way, shape or form
French any way, shape or form French
people other than through paperwork. But
they don't want to admit that because
admitting that is giving a green light
to far-right groups to acknowledge that
the problem that they've been talking
about for years is actually totally
valid. That's the reason why they always
use these very abstract terms. It's
because they don't want to describe what
the actual bad actors are. That's the
reason. So the media, what's the media
going to say when they start killing
their people?
Well, I I again, they're going to say
that it's, you know, it's violence and
turmoil and unrest and all the bad stuff
has to stop happening. That's all
they're that's all they're going to do.
No, you don't understand. Not only do
they know they are the problem, but
specifically says, "Hey, [__] France,"
but the leftists keep trying to appease
them to calm them down. Yeah, of course.
As unions planned a day of nationwide
demonstrations and also strikes over the
budget of Prime Minister Sebastian Loru,
tens of thousands were expected to rally
in Paris and other cities and protesting
students also expressed.
>> Leen has a 16-point lead over her
rivals. I wonder if she's going to be
I wonder if she's going to have the
willingness to do what needs to be done
to get rid of these people. I do. I'm
not sure if she does or not.
I don't know.
No, she won't. She already backtracked.
I
see. Here's the problem is that there
are two archetypes. And there is, and
I'm not just saying that because she's a
woman. There is the female archetype of
the conniving evil empress who is like
Margaret Thatcher or some of these
Chinese empresses, right? That is just
like or Eleanor Roosevelt or somebody
like that. Like there is definitely like
a a female profile for this being valid,
but like there's just really not a lot
of them. Like the one person that I want
to see, we're watching a fail nation and
it's death rattle. No, we're not. This
is guys, this it's really not that bad.
You guys have no idea how bad it can
get. This is nothing.
>> Solidarity with teachers who were on.
>> There's a couple of blocks that are on
fire because some [__] are running
around. It's going to get worse.
>> Over wages and workload.
>> It the issue is our it's our empire, not
theirs. We need to pressure them into
doing things or else they'll be bogged
down in politics. What could be the
solution for EU? the problem exclusively
existential for them.
This would be my this would be what I
would do.
I would literally just get all of these
people that are from these backgrounds
and remove them all from the country.
Period. Any of them that are not net
positive taxpayers that have even the
slightest code violation. Like if you
jaywalked, you're getting sent back. And
if you were born in France, you're going
to get sent to Rwanda. If you you're
going to get sent to the Congo,
I would be sending millions of them back
to random African countries in mass.
Even if they didn't, if their home
countries wouldn't take them, that's
what I would do.
I would do this to millions of them.
Fair? Yeah. It'd be over. And then also
I would go after the people that enabled
it afterwards and I would charge them
for treason.
And we all know what that means.
So why do you think all of this is
happening now? Oh, it's really simple.
So basically the reason why all of this
is happening now is that culturally we
experienced a cultural shift about 50
years ago to where we I we embrace the
idea that bringing in people that are
completely a frictional mis uh they're
like a misalignment with a current
country actually adds texture to a
country rather than coarseness. And
what's happened is that now enough of
those people are in these countries that
they are able to cause chaos and
problems in mass because their numbers
are large enough. Whenever there are
even more of them it's going to be even
worse. So right now what you're seeing
is the tip of the iceberg. But whenever
more of these people come in through
these boats, through these immigration
programs, through refugee and migrant
things, through obviously the fact that
they are having like nine kids at a
time, this problem is only going to keep
getting worse.
It will it's going to keep getting
worse. So that's and and so the reason
why it's happening is that in a lot of
Western countries, they all basically
allowed this to start happening at the
same time. No one has the balls to do
that, though. Everyone's scared to be
hauled a bigot or a racist.
That's true.
Until somebody like Buchi takes over and
he puts everybody in jail
and then all of the [__] uh judges go
to jail, too.
And then he puts all the people that
cause problems away and then there's no
more problems.
It's actually really simple.
So you you you think that nobody has the
balls to do it. You only need one guy to
do it. You don't need a million people
to do this.
We're solely being colonized by our own
doing. We are. That's exactly what's
happening. I think it's more likely that
we'll see France be lost in our
lifetime.
You haven't Haven't you played Age of
Empires?
Do you know that France was like the
dominant military power in all of Europe
for like [__] decades if not
centuries? France had one of the most
vicious and dangerous militaries of all
time.
Was it was that's right it was. And you
know what happened is that those guys
the thing is that doesn't know. Yeah, I
know. And you know what happens? Those
same people have kids and those guys are
still around. You just don't know it
yet.
You just you just don't know it yet.
See, you think to yourself, "Oh, well,
they're all gone." No, they're not. No,
they're not. They're just waiting. And
uh this is when they were Vikings. It's
the same thing as anything else. You'd
really be surprised. Spain. Yes. You'd
really be surprised how fast things are
going to go back to default settings.
And so, yeah, that's what I'd do. I'd
send all these people back and I'd also
but be like Poland might be the solution
too. Yeah. Yeah, I get it. Right. Put me
back in chat. Uh-huh. Right. Bro, I just
saw this tweet. It really is that
simple. Uh, let me see this. I'll pull
it up.
Can I find this?
We are literally arguing with foreigners
as to why we shouldn't give them our
countries. What the [__] are we doing,
fellas? This is a guy that's following
me.
More people are waking up every single
day.
They're waking up every single day. And
I'm very happy to see this. Eventually,
it's going to be too much. Yeah. This is
just insane, man. It really is.
Oh my god. This could be France. Yeah.
No, it will happen to America. It'll
happen. Listen, if you if you let this
happen, it will happen.
This is not something that you know like
you for like all you have to do is just
let anything happen that's going to
happen.
>> Future Dearborn. Yeah, I guess so.
Surprised your PC hasn't crashed again
yet? Don't talk about that.
Sweden is cooked. Yeah, French students.
Oh my god. This is just insane, man. And
uh police are beating the students in
France during manifestations, and one is
at risk of losing an eye. Oh, that's it.
That's it. Oh, man. And uh let's see.
Can I find a few more of these? Holy
[__] The tear gas grenade. This is
another one.
You talking about the AI [__] yet? Not
yet.
>> If we don't do something extreme soon,
this will become all of America.
>> Here's the reality is that that person
in chat is partially right. They are.
They're partially right. This is the
last time that uh there was more France
uh riots.
This is from uh April.
>> Genuine question. What are you doing uh
to help these kinds of situations? You
present your solutions on your platform,
but has it ever helped with these kind
of problems? Yeah, it has because it
normalizes rhetoric and it makes people
open to the idea of taking dramatic
action to solve the problems [music]
rather than a pacified approach that is
condoned by the enemies that want to
subvert you. So, one thing that you need
to understand is that a lot of the
solutions that mainstream media presents
to problems [music] like this are
intentionally designed to not actually
be solutions. They're basically saying
that, you know, okay, your boat's
leaking. Well, instead of fixing the
boat, just start getting a bucket and
then start trying to pour the water out.
So, the reason why I talk about it the
way that I talk about it is I want
people to know and understand that there
is a solution to this that transcends
what is the culturally accepted ways of
discussing the problem. That's the
reason why I'm talking about it. Does
that make sense?
Basically, people that are unhappy. Yes,
exactly. And so that's the reason why I
talk about it in the way that I do is
that I think that by discussing it in
more radical terms and in more dramatic
terms, I normalize the conversations and
I even normalize thinking about it in
those terms. Right? And I think the best
example of this is to go back 10 years
ago. If you go back 10 years ago, a lot
of the conversations and topics and you
know everything that we're getting into
would have been unthinkable. the idea of
remigrating all these different people
uh would have just been unthinkable.
Nobody could be elected by saying that.
And now it's like the top issue. The
main issue of you know certain different
immigrant communities just simply not
assimilating and then you needing to
remove them because of that and them
committing fraud on a mass scale. This
would be unthinkable to discuss 10 years
ago because it would have been
reclassified as racism totally. So the
goal really is not about and and and who
really took a wrecking ball to that? It
was Donald Trump. Donald Trump was the
one that really shifted the Overton
window and he changed the frame of
reference of what people can discuss and
how it can be discussed. Now obviously I
can't do anything remotely close to
that. that I can do what I can do, which
is continue conversations and saying
things that I think lead to a position
that people feel more comfortable
actually solving a problem like this in
a definitive in a in a definite way
rather than simply uh you know a managed
decline. I think that a lot of media's
solutions for this and even Democratic
solutions for this, especially
Democratic solutions for this is
accepting that it won't happen to you
that fast, so it won't be that bad.
Uh Trump must change the world. They
did. So, does that make does that make
sense like why I do this and what I'm
saying? Right. And uh so yeah, and Nick
Shirley would have been banned 10 years
ago. Yeah. Nick Shirley would have been
banned 10 years ago and he would have
been deplatformed everywhere for
obviously promoting racism.
So, and again, we have things like this,
right? Uh, immigration judge allows DHS
to deport Islamic Society of Milwaukee's
president. This is this would have been
unthinkable 10 years ago.
It would have been unthinkable 10 years
ago. And now, not only is it something
that we're discussing, but it's
something that's normalized. It's
normalized and people are celebrating
it. So again, like that's really how I
would look at any of this. Is this
another one? Oh my god.
>> The people power said, "Well, if it's
happening, it doesn't matter because
I'll be dead by the time it affects me."
Yes.
So,
Look at all that. It's insane, man. It
really is.